My name is Nick [surname unclear]. I'm 25 years
old. My job at Sarasota Ford is a service
porter where I prep cars and get them ready to
sell.
My name is Beaver Shriver and I'm the founder of
Inclusion Revolution.
If I asked you where do people with disabilities
work and you'd say
Publix and you'd say Goodwill and then you'd be
stuck because they just
don't get the opportunities. So now all the big
push behind Inclusion Revolution is
to find those job opportunities and then match
the job that's available with our
participants. We help the employer learn how to
accommodate somebody with a
disability and then we get Sarah or Jimmy or
whomever ready for that job so
that when they walk in they've already got some
skills and they're ready to
rock it. I met Nick and Sarah six months ago and
I learned that Nick was the best
detail guy they ever had so I thought well I
know exactly who I'm going to
call to see what we can set up. We were so so so
thankful for Nick to have an
opportunity to do something that he loved and
you know a lot of that is due to
Beaver going in to Sarasota Ford really telling
them about Nick. This is
probably one of the first jobs where Nick is so
supported by all of the
employees and by his supervisor that he doesn't
even have a job coach at this
point. Nick has been doing a wonderful job he's
extremely consistent. The team
has become very close either you know in the car
a lot together chatting they
go to lunch together as well with Nick. I first
met Nick a couple days into him
being on our team. We drive listening music he
talks about what he likes I
can't wait to have another person like him on
the team and I know Nick is just
going to continue to thrive on his job and
continue to inspire people that
Sarasota Ford and beyond. My name is Sebastian
Nick's been working with us
for a couple months now he's been really really
helpful and he does an
amazing job cleaning it detailing it's just it's
just awesome to have on
my team. So my name is also Sebastian I work
with Nick in the loaner department
here at Sarasota Ford. It's actually impressive
how fast he learned how to do
all these things with these loaner vehicles. I
would even say that he
actually learned faster than I did in the past.
Doing my job is fun. A big thank
you to Beaver for getting my job at Sarasota
Ford. My name is Kevin and I
work at Sarasota Ford. I used to do detailing a
lot but Nick is by far the
best in my opinion. I think every dealership
needs somebody like Nick.